Register of the Fenton Stratton Jacobs papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1944-1952
  - 1948
    - Oyer, G. (Box-folder 7: 39)
    - Palmer, J. W. (Box-folder 7: 40)
    - Parks, F. L. (Box-folder 7: 41)
    - Paul, Willard S. (Box-folder 7: 42)
    - Philadelphia Quartermaster Department (Box-folder 7: 43)
    - Philpot, E. W. (Box-folder 7: 44)
    - Pierce, C. A. (Box-folder 7: 45)
    - Pittman, L. G. (Box-folder 7: 46)
    - Plank, Ewart G. (Box-folder 7: 47)
    - Port Transportation Officer, Fort Mason (Box-folder 7: 48)
    - Poundstone, A. F. (Box-folder 7: 49)
    - Presidio of San Francisco (Box-folder 7: 50)
    - Propeller Club (Box-folder 7: 51)
    - Redling (Box-folder 7: 52)
    - Rehm, H. W. (Box-folder 7: 53)
    - Roberts, Thomas D. (Box-folder 7: 54)
    - Roe, Theodore J. (Box-folder 7: 55)
    - Rooks, John M. (Box-folder 7: 56)
    - Ross, Frank S. (Box-folder 7: 57)
    - Royer, M. L. (Box-folder 7: 58)
    - Ruffner, Clark L. (Box-folder 7: 59)
    - Rutledge, Robert E. (Box-folder 7: 60)
    - San Francisco Port of Embarkation (Box-folder 7: 61)
    - Scheinman, J. B. (Box-folder 7: 62)
    - Schluter, Paul (Box-folder 7: 63)
    - Schramm, Ned (Box-folder 7: 64)
    - Schwyter (Box-folder 7: 65)
    - Sears, R. R. (Box-folder 7: 66)
    - Sears Roebuck (Box-folder 7: 67)
    - Siegel, Sidney H. (Box-folder 7: 68)
    - Slaughter, P. H. (Box-folder 7: 69)
    - Smith, J. M. (Box-folder 7: 70)
    - Smithers, S. W. (Box-folder 7: 71)
    - Smoak, Robert A. (Box-folder 7: 72)
    - Spiltz, Allan G. (Box-folder 7: 73)
    - Stewart, George C. (Box-folder 7: 74)
    - Stoddard, C. S. (Box-folder 7: 75)
    - Stranacher, Robert (Box-folder 7: 76)
    - Stratton, L. C. (Box-folder 7: 77)
    - Stratton, M. A. (Box-folder 7: 78)
    - Stuart, R. W. (Box-folder 7: 79)
    - Sumner, E. M. (Box-folder 7: 80)
    - Sutherland, Adam (Box-folder 7: 81)
    - Swedish Consul (Box-folder 7: 82)
    - Swope, John G. (Box-folder 7: 83)
    - Townes, Morton E. (Box-folder 7: 84)
    - Tufte, T. B. (Box-folder 7: 85)
    - Tyng, Francis C. (Box-folder 7: 86)
    - Vaughan, Harry B. (Box-folder 7: 87)
    - Ventress, Robert H. (Box-folder 7: 88)
    - Wafford, Lloyd (Box-folder 7: 89)
    - Warren, Ross (Box-folder 7: 90)
    - Weaver, W. G. (Box-folder 7: 91)
    - Weed, Thomas J. (Box-folder 7: 92)
    - Whitcomb, George M. (Box-folder 7: 93)
    - Whitcomb, Richard S. (Box-folder 7: 94)
    - Wilder, C. J. (Box-folder 7: 95)
    - Williams, E. A. (Box-folder 7: 96)
    - Williams, Edward W. (Box-folder 8: 1)
    - Williams, Worthington (Box-folder 8: 2)
    - Witt, Milton W. (Box-folder 8: 3)
    - Wooster, H. A. (Box-folder 8: 4)
    - Wooten, R. H. (Box-folder 8: 5)
    - Wylie, Robert H. (Box-folder 8: 6)
    - Young, Audrey P. (Box-folder 8: 7)
  - 1949
    - Arbuthnott, Hugh (Box-folder 8: 8)
    - Armored School (Box-folder 8: 9)
    - Arnold, Lester (Box-folder 8: 10)
    - Barbat, R. (Box-folder 8: 11)
    - Blake, Christopher (Box-folder 8: 12)
    - Boyd, Roy V. (Box-folder 8: 13)
    - Bradley, Roland H. (Box-folder 8: 14)
    - Breeden, Edward V. (Box-folder 8: 15)
    - Brockman, J. D. (Box-folder 8: 16)
    - de la Cerna, James F. (Box-folder 8: 17)
    - Clampett, Robert D. (Box-folder 8: 18)
    - Clearihue, Cornelia L. (Box-folder 8: 19)
    - Conner, R. T. (Box-folder 8: 20)
    - Conyers, Kit C. (Box-folder 8: 21)
    - Danin, C. A. (Box-folder 8: 22)
    - Dann, Clifford H. (Box-folder 8: 23)
    - Dawson, Allan W. (Box-folder 8: 24)
    - Descamps, Edouard (Box-folder 8: 25)
    - Giard, Jacques E. (Box-folder 8: 26)
    - Granger (Box-folder 8: 27)
    - Hacking, Fred L. (Box-folder 8: 28)
    - Healy, Barbara Ann (Box-folder 8: 29)
    - Henderson, Chester T. (Box-folder 8: 30)
    - Irons, A. L. (Box-folder 8: 31)
    - Keller, W. H. (Box-folder 8: 32)
    - Kleinman, Edward A. (Box-folder 8: 33)
    - Kling, Charles J. (Box-folder 8: 34)
    - Lee, Can (Box-folder 8: 35)
    - Lester, James A. (Box-folder 8: 36)
    - Lyter, Clinton S. (Box-folder 8: 37)
    - Mandell, Harold (Box-folder 8: 38)
    - Manufacturer's Life Insurance Company (Box-folder 8: 39)
    - McAuliffe, Regina M. (Box-folder 8: 40)
    - Pierce, C. T. (Box-folder 8: 41)
    - Pittman, Marjorie L. (Box-folder 8: 42)
    - Plank, Ewart G. (Box-folder 8: 43)
    - Puntenney, William H. (Box-folder 8: 44)
    - Rainier Club (Box-folder 8: 45)
    - Richmond Blues Border Veterans (Box-folder 8: 46)
    - Rose, William C. (Box-folder 8: 47)
    - Rosenthal, S. M. (Box-folder 8: 48)
    - Sampson, Mary Eustice (Box-folder 8: 49)
    - San Diego County (Box-folder 8: 50)
    - Selcer, Jules (Box-folder 8: 51)
    - Seward, Oscar (Box-folder 8: 52)
    - Smith, Wayne C. (Box-folder 8: 53)
    - Snider, Henry R. (Box-folder 8: 54)
    - Spitz, Allan G. (Box-folder 8: 55)
    - Stevens, J. (Box-folder 8: 56)
    - Stratton, M. A. (Box-folder 8: 57)
    - Tapner, John (Box-folder 8: 58)
    - War Department (Box-folder 8: 59)
  - 1950
    - Alaska Freight Lines (Box-folder 8: 60)
    - Back, George I. (Box-folder 8: 61)
    - Barbey (Box-folder 8: 62)
    - Bayard, William C. (Box-folder 8: 63)
    - Bendetson, Karl R. (Box-folder 8: 64)
    - Besson, F. S. (Box-folder 8: 65)
    - Brown, E. H. (Box-folder 8: 66)
    - Byers, Clovis (Box-folder 8: 67)
    - Carmel Lots (Box-folder 8: 68)
    - Christmas, Thomas W. E. (Box-folder 8: 69)
    - Cole, Ashley T. (Box-folder 8: 70)
    - Cole, John T. (Box-folder 8: 71)
    - Crittenberger, Willis D. (Box-folder 8: 72)
    - Day, John W. (Box-folder 8: 73)
    - Devine, James D. (Box-folder 8: 74)
    - Eastwood, Harold E. (Box-folder 8: 75)
    - Eichelberger, Robert L. (Box-folder 8: 76)
    - Finnesey, K. H. (Box-folder 8: 77)
    - Gibney, Lou (Box-folder 8: 78)
    - Gilmore, Jerry (Box-folder 8: 79)
    - Granger, Judie (Box-folder 8: 80)
    - Green, Mack M. (Box-folder 8: 81)
    - Harrington, George C. (Box-folder 8: 82)
    - Hayford, Bertram F. (Box-folder 8: 83)
    - Heileman, Frank A. (Box-folder 8: 84)
    - Hobbs, Leland S. (Box-folder 8: 85)
    - Hughes, Allen P. (Box-folder 8: 86)
    - Hyde, S. F. (Box-folder 8: 87)
    - Kleinman, Edward A. (Box-folder 8: 88)
    - Kolar, Richard V. (Box-folder 8: 89)
    - Lawton, Henry R. (Box-folder 8: 90)
    - Lee, John C. H. (Box-folder 8: 91)
    - Macauley, T. C. (Box-folder 8: 92)
    - McAuliffe, Regina (Box-folder 8: 93)
    - Minier, Earl F. (Box-folder 8: 94)
    - Palmer, J. W. (Box-folder 8: 95)
    - Phyfe, H. L. (Box-folder 8: 96)
    - Rehm, Harold W. (Box-folder 8: 97)
    - Tapner, John (Box-folder 8: 98)
    - Taylor and Sledd Inc. (Box-folder 8: 99)
    - Taylor, Erquiet (Box-folder 8: 100)
    - Wainwright, James M. (Box-folder 9: 1)
    - Walther, Norris E. (Box-folder 9: 2)
    - Wester, Carl (Box-folder 9: 3)
    - Wrenn, Grover (Box-folder 9: 4)
    - Yount, Paul F. (Box-folder 9: 5)
  - 1951
    - Bolte, Charles L. (Box-folder 9: 6)
    - Breeden, E. V. (Box-folder 9: 7)
    - Cave, Glenn E. (Box-folder 9: 8)
    - Cutcheon, Robert L. (Box-folder 9: 9)
    - Decker, Silas E. (Box-folder 9: 10)
    - Devin, William F. (Box-folder 9: 11)
    - DeWitt, Calvin (Box-folder 9: 12)
    - DeWitt, Wilmer W. (Box-folder 9: 13)
    - Donaldson, V. (Box-folder 9: 14)
    - Duffie, Harold R. (Box-folder 9: 15)
    - Eastwood, Harold E. (Box-folder 9: 16)
    - Evans, Nile (Box-folder 9: 17)
    - Granger, Judie (Box-folder 9: 18)
    - Gunn, George (Box-folder 9: 19)
    - Harris, Ken (Box-folder 9: 20)
    - Harrold, Clinton (Box-folder 9: 21)
    - Heileman, Frank A. (Box-folder 9: 22)
    - Hobbs, Leland S. (Box-folder 9: 23)
    - Jackson, Montgomery C. (Box-folder 9: 24)
    - Jones, Winston J. (Box-folder 9: 25)
    - Kleinman, Edward A. (Box-folder 9: 26)
    - Langlie, Arthur B. (Box-folder 9: 27)
    - Leavey, Ed (Box-folder 9: 28)
    - Lee, Can (Box-folder 9: 29)
    - Lee, John C. H. (Box-folder 9: 30)
    - Lester, James A. (Box-folder 9: 31)
    - Luplow, Kenneth J. (Box-folder 9: 32)
    - Mckay, Douglas (Box-folder 9: 33)
    - Milton, Ray C. (Box-folder 9: 34)
    - Minier, Earl F. (Box-folder 9: 35)
    - Oyer, Harry (Box-folder 9: 36)
    - Palmer, J. W. (Box-folder 9: 37)
    - Philpot, E. W. (Box-folder 9: 38)
    - Pittman, L. C. (Box-folder 9: 39)
    - Plank, Ewart G. (Box-folder 9: 40)
    - Rehm, H. W. (Box-folder 9: 41)
    - Seattle Port of Embarkation (Box-folder 9: 42)
    - Seattle Yacht Club (Box-folder 9: 43)
    - Smith, Warren G. (Box-folder 9: 44)
    - Sweeney, Joseph A. (Box-folder 9: 45)
    - Taylor, Erquiet (Box-folder 9: 46)
    - Wedemeyer, A. C. (Box-folder 9: 47)
    - Yount, Paul (Box-folder 9: 48)
  - 1952
    - Appel, C. (Box-folder 9: 49)
    - Arbuthnott, Hugh (Box-folder 9: 50)
    - Baker, David A. (Box-folder 9: 51)
    - Baker, Frayne (Box-folder 9: 52)
    - Besson, F. S. (Box-folder 9: 53)
    - Bill (Box-folder 9: 54)
    - Black, E. A. (Box-folder 9: 55)
    - Boon, W. W. (Box-folder 9: 56)
    - Breeden, Edward V. (Box-folder 9: 57)
    - Callaghan, W. M. (Box-folder 9: 58)
    - Casalis, Henri A. (Box-folder 9: 59)
    - Connor, Edward H. (Box-folder 9: 60)
    - Cosah, A. H. (Box-folder 9: 61)
    - Credit Union, Seattle Port of Embarkation (Box-folder 9: 62)
    - Cuff, Tom (Box-folder 9: 63)
    - Descamps, Edouard (Box-folder 9: 64)
    - DeWitt, Calvin (Box-folder 9: 65)
    - DeWitt, Wilmer W. (Box-folder 9: 66)
    - Dietl, George (Box-folder 9: 67)
    - Dudley, C. R. (Box-folder 9: 68)
    - Earl, James P. (Box-folder 9: 69)
    - Eastman, George D. (Box-folder 9: 70)
    - Eaton, M. E. (Box-folder 9: 71)
    - Egarton, Ashley (Box-folder 9: 72)
    - Eraxton, Freddie Marie (Box-folder 9: 73)
    - Faure, Andre (Box-folder 9: 74)
    - Finn, Joseph Earl (Box-folder 9: 75)
    - Gerhardt, C. H. (Box-folder 9: 76)
    - Granger, Hugh (Box-folder 9: 77)
    - Harris, Tom (Box-folder 9: 78)
    - Heileman, Bob (Box-folder 9: 79)
    - Helbock, R. P. (Box-folder 9: 80)
    - Hyde, S. F. (Box-folder 10: 1)
    - Jarvis, Jack (Box-folder 10: 2)
    - Johnson, Edwin L. (Box-folder 10: 3)
    - Karolevitz, R. F. (Box-folder 10: 4)
    - Kilpatrick, John (Box-folder 10: 5)
    - Leroy (Box-folder 10: 6)
    - Matson, Paul H. (Box-folder 10: 7)
    - Matteson, James S. (Box-folder 10: 8)
    - McAuliffe, Anthony C. (Box-folder 10: 9)
    - McKinstry, M. (Box-folder 10: 10)
    - Military Sea Transportation Service (Box-folder 10: 11)
    - Milton, R. C. (Box-folder 10: 12)
    - Nolestein, James (Box-folder 10: 13)
    - Plank, Ewart G. (Box-folder 10: 14)
    - Postmaster, S. F. (Box-folder 10: 15)
    - Rehm, Harold W. (Box-folder 10: 16)
    - Ries, Arthur W. (Box-folder 10: 17)
    - Sabin, L. S. (Box-folder 10: 18)
    - Seattle Yacht Club (Box-folder 10: 19)
    - Selcer, Jules (Box-folder 10: 20)
    - Sousa, Eddie (Box-folder 10: 21)
    - Sutherland, Jack V. (Box-folder 10: 22)
    - Swing, Joseph M. (Box-folder 10: 23)
    - United States Department of the Navy (Box-folder 10: 24)
    - Van (Box-folder 10: 25)
    - Vandenberg, R. E. (Box-folder 10: 26)
    - Wagner, John G. (Box-folder 10: 27)
    - Weed, T. J. (Box-folder 10: 28)
    - Wilson, Vernard (Box-folder 10: 29)
    - Yount, Paul F. (Box-folder 10: 30)
- Speeches and Writings, 1926-1945
  - "Address at Channel Base Section,", 1945 February 26 (Box-folder 10: 31)
  - "Address at French Officers' and Enlisted Men's Dances in Fontainebleau,", 1944 September 9 (Box-folder 10: 32)
  - "Address to Mayor and People of St. Addresse,", 1944 November 11 (Box-folder 10: 33)
  - "The Arapahoe Hunt-- Colorado,", 1941 (Box-folder 10: 34)
  - Cavalry Combat, 1937 (Box-folder 10: 35-37, 11: 1-2)
  - Chicago Sunday Tribune, "Horsemanship,", 1927 (Box-folder 10: 38)
  - "Courtesies and Customs of the Service,", circa 1945 (Box-folder 10: 39)
  - "Gates of Horses,", 1926 October (Box-folder 10: 40)
  - Monterey Peninsula Herald Horsemanship articles, 1945 (Box-folder 10: 41)
- Photographs, circa 1925-1952
  - Cavalry, 1942 (Box-folder 11: 3)
  - Ceremony at Lille, France, circa 1944 (Box-folder 11: 4)
  - General MacArthur at Seattle Port of Embarkation, circa 1952 (Box-folder 11: 5)
  - Press photos, circa 1925 (Box-folder 11: 6)
- Printed Matter, 1912-1964
  - "Address by Major General Edmond H. Leavey, Chief of Transportation, Before the American Merchant Marine Conference and Twentieth Annual Convention of the Propeller Clug of the United States,", 1946 October 16 (Box-folder 11: 7)
  - Armor, 1958 (Box-folder 11: 8)
  - Army, 1964 (Box-folder 11: 9)
  - Army Information Digest, 1952 (Box-folder 11: 10)
  - "Atlas of the World Battle Fronts in Semimonthly Phases,", 1945 (Box-folder 11: 11)
  - Bridle Bits, 1929 (Box-folder 11: 12)
  - Cavalry Journal, 1925-1942 (Box-folder 11: 13)
  - Cavalry School manuals, 1912-1937 (Box-folder 11: 14, 12: 1-6, 13: 1-8)
  - Dictionary, circa 1950 (Box-folder 13: 9)
  - Field message book, 1917 (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - Forty Years After: An Appreciation of the Genius of Edward Henry Harriman (1848-1909), 1949 (Box-folder 14: 2)
  - The Horse, 1931 (Box-folder 14: 3)
  - Korea, circa 1950 (Box-folder 14: 4)
  - The Living Age, 1929 (Box-folder 14: 5)
  - Majestic Atlas of the World, 1933 (Box-folder 14: 6)
  - Military School manual, 1917 (Box-folder 14: 7)
  - Model Messes of the ETO, circa 1940 (Box-folder 14: 8)
  - Omaha Beachhead, 1945 (Box-folder 14: 9)
  - Our Army, 1935 (Box-folder 14: 10)
  - Retired Army Bulletin, 1960 (Box-folder 14: 11)
  - San Francisco Chronicle special issues on Bay Bridge and Port, 1936 (Box-folder 14: 12-14)
  - Seattle Port of Embarkation materials, 1945 (Box-folder 15: 1-2)
  - "Sordet's Cavalry Corps,", 1937 (Box-folder 15: 3)
  - State Historical Markers of Virginia, 1937 (Box-folder 15: 4)
  - The Remount, 1930 (Box-folder 15: 5)
  - "The Tanaka Memorial: An Outline Presented to the Japanese Emperor by Premier Tanaka for the Japanese Conquest of China and other Nations,", circa 1950 (Box-folder 15: 6)
  - "Voice of SHAEF to Foreign Workers in the Ruhr, Rheinisch-Westphalia and Rhineland,", 1944 (Box-folder 15: 7)
- Oversize Material, 1910-1950
  - "Gen Jacobs watching the arrival of the new Simon B. Buckner,", circa 1950 (Box-folder 16: 1)
  - "Maps to Illustrate Cavalry Operations in the World War,", undated (Box-folder 16: 2)
  - Military and topographic maps of Europe and the American Southwest, circa 1910-1950 (Map case)
  - San Francisco Port of Embarkation manuals, 1948 (Box-folder 16: 3)
  - Seattle Port of Embarkation manuals, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 16: 4-5)